<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Thunderbird Marching Band</title>
    <description>The Thunderbird Marching Band is UBC&#39;s premier music and spirit group! We perform at Thunderbirds games and at other events throughout UBC and the Lower Mainland. Musicians of all skill levels are welcome to join!</description>
    <link>/</link>
    <atom:link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Retreat 2015</title>
        <description>
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 13 Apr 2015 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>/news/retreat/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/news/retreat/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>2014-15 Award Winners</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;We are proud to present the following awards for 2014-15:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;section-of-the-year&quot;&gt;Section of the Year&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The &lt;em&gt;Section of the Year&lt;/em&gt; award is given annually to the TMB section that demonstrates the utmost levels of commitment, dedication, musicality, and spirit to the band. The band is proud to present this year’s award to the &lt;strong&gt;Percussion&lt;/strong&gt; section, with members Johnny Zollars, Maria Chen,  Adrian Lee, Nicolas Moss,  Tina Shi, Valeria Suarez Gomez, and  Vivienne Zhang.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;harold-king-award&quot;&gt;Harold King Award&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The &lt;em&gt;Harold King Award&lt;/em&gt;, named after author of “The U.B.C. March” Harold King, is given annually to a TMB member who demonstrates excellent levels of commitment, dedication, and spirit in their service to the band. A member may only receive this award once. The band is proud to present this year’s award to percussionist &lt;strong&gt;Vivienne Zhang&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;rookie-of-the-year&quot;&gt;Rookie of the Year&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The &lt;em&gt;Rookie of the Year&lt;/em&gt; award is given to the first-year band member who exhibits exemplary musical talent and dedication in their service to the band. The band is proud to present this year’s award to first-year trombonist &lt;strong&gt;Jonathan Zhang&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 12 Apr 2015 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>/news/award-winners/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/news/award-winners/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>New Exec</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Our members voted, and the results are in! The Thunderbird Marching Band’s executive for 2015-16 is:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Presidnt:&lt;/strong&gt; Vivienne Zhang&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Drum Major:&lt;/strong&gt; Fred Cholowski&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Treasurer:&lt;/strong&gt; Max Bogard&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Secretary:&lt;/strong&gt; Nicolas Moss&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Publicity Officer:&lt;/strong&gt; Jessica Hohner&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Logistics Officer:&lt;/strong&gt; Nicolas Moss&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We look forward to leading the band to great heights this season!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2015 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>/news/new-exec/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/news/new-exec/</guid>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
